Finding Aid for School of Social Work (University of Michigan) Records 1935-2010
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Correspondence, 1958-1986
  - University
    - University Presidents
      - Harold Shapiro, 1977-1984 (Box 5)
    - Vice-President for Academic Affairs
      - Carolyn Davis, 1976-1980 (Box 5)
      - Richard A. English, 1974-1980 (Box 5)
      - Billy E. Frye, 1980-1986 (Box 5)
      - Roger Heyns, 1962-1964 (Box 5)
      - James Lesch, 1965-1975 (Box 5)
      - Frank H. Rhodes, 1975-1977; 2 folders (Box 5)
      - John H. Romani, 1971-1974 (Box 5)
      - Allan F. Smith, 1964-1979; 2 folders (Box 5)
      - Alfred Sussman, 1980 (Box 5)
    - Vice-President for Research
      - Charles G. Overberger, 1973-1982 (Box 5)
    - Vice-President for State Relations and Planning, Fedele F. Fauri, 1968-1973 (Box 5)
  - Non-University
    - Michigan Department of Mental Health, 1959-1978 (Box 5)
    - Michigan Department of Social Services, 1964-1978; 2 folders (Box 5)
    - University Deans of Social Work, 1971 (Box 5)
    - Washtenaw County Community Mental Health Center, 1968-1978 (Box 5)
- Topical Files, 1935-1996; 4.5 linear feet
  The Topical Files series consists of alphabetically arranged subject files covering a broad spectrum of administrative and policy issues. The series is comprised of three separate alphabetical subseries, reflecting different accession in which the materials were received by the library. The subseries overlap both chronologically and in subject matter.
  - 1950-1984
    The Topical Files, 1950-1984 subseries, (2 linear feet) is arranged alphabetically and includes files on affirmative action programs, budgets, school history, reaccreditation, and various reports. Reaccreditation includes materials from both the 1973 and 1983 reviews as well as the printed final reports.
    - Annual Reports, 1948-1951 (Box 6)
    - Affirmative Action Program, 1969-1972; 2 folders (Box 6)
    - Affirmative Action Program for Women, 1971 (Box 6)
    - Budgetary Materials, 1946-1954; 1969-1980; 13 folders (Box 6)
    - Class Sizes, 1964-1966 (Box 6)
    - Community Practice Lab Evaluation, 1971 (Box 6)
    - County Welfare Agencies Survey Questionnaire, "To Provide Hope", circa 1968 (Box 6)
    - Faculty Data (Notebook), 1970-1980 (Box 6)
    - Faculty Manual of Policies and Procedures, circa, 1972 (Box 6)
    - Financial Aid, 1958-1976 (Box 6)
    - Follow-Up Study of Graduates, 1973 (Box 6)
    - History of the School of Social Work, 2 folders; 1 volumes scrapbook (Box 7)
    - HUD Model Cities Grant, 1969-1970 (Box 7)
    - Michigan Council on Human Service Education, 1974 (Box 7)
    - Minority-Relevent Content, 1973-1980; 2 folders (Box 7)
      (re: utilization of minority resources in the School of Social Work)
    - Program in Social Work Administration, 1963 (Box 7)
    - Public Policy Research and Administration (proposal), 1968 (Box 7)
    - Re-accreditation
      - General (Box 7)
      - Final Reports
        - 1973 (Box 7)
        - 1983 (Box 7)
    - Regents Communications, 1964-1970 (Box 7)
    - Reports
      - Admission Criteria, Task Force on, 1972-1973 (Box 7)
      - Advisory Council on Public Administration to the Executive Committee, 1967 (Box 7)
    - University Consortium Center (Grand Rapids, MI), 1974-1978 (Box 7)
    - University of Michigan Sesquicentennial, 1963-1967 (Box 7)
  - 1939-1992, 1.5 linear feet
    The Topical Files, 1939-1992, subseries (1.5 linear feet) is arranged alphabetically by subject and contains records of various activities within the School of Social Work. The material in these files ranges from reports and proposals to correspondence.
    Of particular interest are the Council for Social Work Education (CSWE) files. These include annual reports submitted by the University of Michigan to CSWE from 1939 to 1983. They include a great deal of statistical information concerning the School of Social Work. Information ranges from faculty and student statistics to grant support and graduation data. Also included in this subseries is a folder of materials for the Annual Meeting in Detroit in 1984 for which Harold Johnson served as chairman of the Plenary Session Subcommittee. Reports prepared for the school's reaccreditation review in 1963 are also included.
    The reaccreditation folders contain memos, correspondence and supporting documentation for the school's 1973 and 1983 reaccreditation reviews. The work of university-wide committees is evidenced in the Intercollegiate Athletics Committee, an ad hoc committee appointed by President Harold Shapiro, and Martin Luther King Symposium folders. Johnson served as the chair for both of these committees.
    - Annual Reports, 1940-1987; 2 folders (Box 9)
    - Budgetary Materials, 1970-1972 (Box 9)
    - Cohen Symposium and Fellowships, 1987-1988 (Box 9)
    - Council for Social Work Education
      - Annual Meeting (Detroit), 1984; 1983-1984 (Box 9)
      - Curriculum Policy Statement, 1981-1982 (Box 9)
      - Faculty Salary Information (Annual Report), 1958-1975 (Box 9)
      - Handbook of Accreditation Standards and Procedures (1987 Revisions) (Box 9)
      - News/Symposium Releases, 1976-1981 (Box 9)
      - Report of On-Campus Visit, 1963 (Box 9)
      - Report Prepared by UM School of Social Work, 1963 (Box 9)
      - Statistics of Social Work (Annual Report), 1939-1951 (Box 9)
      - Statistics of Social Work (Annual Report), 1952-1983; 5 folders (Box 10)
    - Curriculum Revision, CAPE and IP, 1976-1984 (Box 10)
    - Divisional Structures, 1973-1974 (Box 10)
    - Doctoral Program in Social Work and Social Sciences
      - Program Proposals and Changes, 1956-1992 (Box 10)
      - Review Committee Report, 1982 (Box 10)
      - Twenty-fifth Anniversary Subcommittee, 1979-1982 (Box 10)
    - External Review, 1980 (Box 10)
    - Financial Aid, 1964-1978 (Box 10)
    - Flint Campus, 1981-1982 (Box 10)
    - Human Subjects Review Committee, 1969-1978 (Box 10)
    - Institute of Gerontology, 1981-1988 (Box 10)
    - Intercollegiate Athletics, 1986-1988 (Box 10)
    - Kellogg International Program on Health and Aging, 1989 (Box 10)
    - External Review, 1980 (Box 10)
    - Library Committee, 1981-1985 (Box 10)
    - Management Incentives Task Force, 1984 (Box 10)
    - Martin Luther King Symposium, 1986-1987 (Box 10)
    - Reaccreditation, 1973; 1981-1985; 2 folders (Box 10)
    - Standing Committee Lists, 1960-1977 (Box 10)
    - University of Iowa, 1986-1987 (Box 10)
  - 1935-1996
    The Topical Files, 1935-1996, subseries documents a range of topics and includes information on policies and procedures as well as reports.
    - Annual Reports of the Office of Research Development, 1984-1987 (Box 25)
    - Black Action Movement (BAM), 1970 (Box 25)
    - Coalition of Asian Social Workers, 1984 (Box 25)
    - Continuing Education Program, 1973-1975 (Box 25)
    - Faculty Handbook Additions, 1987-1992 (Box 25)
    - Faculty Handbook of Policies and Procedures, Additions
      - 1972-1977 (Box 25)
      - 1987 (Box 25)
    - Field Instruction Manual, 1970 (Box 25)
    - General Correspondence
      - 1946-1966 (Box 25)
      - 1966-1974 (Box 25)
    - Government Relations, 1993-1995 (Box 25)
    - Grading Practices, 1966-1974 (Box 25)
    - Handbook for New Instructional Staff Members, Special Faculty, and Teaching Assistants, 1979 (Box 25)
    - Interdisciplinary Seminar on the Future of Social Work, 1986-1987 (Box 25)
    - Korean International Symposium, "Aging and Welfare for the Aged,", 1984-1987 (Box 25)
    - Lewis, Edith-Correspondence, 1990-1991 (Box 25)
    - List of Masters Theses, 1935-1969 (Box 25)
    - Manual of Policies and Procedures
      - 1969 (Box 26)
      - 1972 (Box 26)
      - 1980 (Box 26)
    - Merrill Palmer School, 1943-1944 (Box 26)
    - News Releases, 1994-1996 (Box 26)
    - Registration Material, 1991 (Box 26)
    - Reports
      - Committee to Review the Joint Doctoral Program in Social Work and Social Science,", 1982 (Box 26)
      - (Prepared for the) Council on Social Work Education, 1963 (Box 26)
      - Final Report on Prevention Training in Social Work, 1989 (Box 26)
      - Michigan Jail Removal Assessment: 1992 Final Report, 1993 (Box 26)
      - The Multicultural Forum circa 1993 and The Future of Social Work and Social Work Education, 1988 (Box 26)
      - Show Cause Materials, 1984 (Box 26)
      - Training for a Sense of Community and Successful Careers, 1991 (Box 26)
    - Report: Unilateral Family Therapy for Alcohol Abuse, 1991 (Box 26)
    - Sage Foundation, 1959-1967 (Box 26)
    - Social Work Alumni Society Constitution, circa 1995 (Box 26)
    - Strategic Planning Report, 1987 (Box 26)
    - Student Advising, 1975 (Box 26)
    - Student Union Constitution, 1967-1972 (Box 26)
    - Student Union Newsletter scattered, 1973-1981 (Box 26)
    - Summary of the Report to Council on Social Word Education, 1973 (Box 26)
    - Support Staff Handbook, 1979 (Box 26)
    - Undergraduate Social Work Program, 1964-1977 (Box 26)
  - 1983-2000
    The Topical Files (1.25 linear feet, 1983-2000) contain a variety of subjects, including material on the changing computing environment within the school, surveys of graduates, and strategic planning materials from the late 1980s.
    - Alumni Society Annual Meeting
      - 1983-1994 (Box 31)
      - 1995 (Box 31)
    - Computer Advisory Committee, 1990-1995 (Box 31)
    - Computing Needs and Resources, 1988-1989 (Box 31)
    - Computer Resource Committee, 1985-1987 (Box 31)
    - Data Displays, 1991 (Box 31)
    - Minority Relevant Content Resources, 1979-1981 (Box 31)
    - Project STaR (Service, Training and Research in Jewish Communal Development), 1995-2000; 2 folders (Box 31)
    - South African Initiative, 1990-1992 (Box 31)
    - Strategic Plan, Report, August 1990 (Box 31)
    - Strategic Planning Committee, 1985-1989 (Box 31)
    - Survey of Graduates, 1983-1993 (Box 31)
    - University of Ghana, Linkage Project, 1990-1993 (Box 31)
- Group Work Program, 1946-1970
  The Group Work Program series (2.0 linear feet) dates from 1946 to 1970. Group Work is based on social science and social psychology. During Group Work the social worker acts as an outside force to affect the actions and thinking of the group instead of becoming a part of the group. This series includes three subseries: Administration, Faculty Papers, and Case Studies. Each of these subseries are arranged alphabetically. The Administration subseries contains records of the course work, curriculum, and lists of faculty papers. The Faculty Papers subseries is arranged alphabetically by faculty names. Some of the papers have been published. The Case Study subseries contains case studies done on group work during this time at the university and is arranged alphabetically by topic. There are also three reel-to-reel audio tapes which are included in the records.
  - Administration
    - Classroom Materials, 1966-1969 (Box 11)
    - Curriculum, 1961-1967 (Box 11)
    - Lists of Faculty Group Work Papers, 1961-1967 (Box 11)
    - School of Social Work Report, 1963 (Box 11)
  - Faculty Papers
    - Bertcher, Harvey
      - audio tape, undated; Reel-to-reel, 3 1/2 ips (Box 11)
      - 1966 (Box 11)
      - 1969 (Box 11)
    - Borenzweig, Herman, no date (Box 11)
    - Brim, Orville G., 1960 (Box 11)
    - Carter, Beryl L., 1970 (Box 11)
    - Churchill, Sallie R
      - 1959 (Box 11)
      - 1962 (Box 11)
      - 1964 (Box 11)
      - 1965 (Box 11)
    - Churchill, Sallie R. and Glasser, Paul H., 1965 (Box 11)
    - Connor, Alan N. and Brinks, Kenneth L., 1969 (Box 11)
    - Craxton, Tom A., 1966 (Box 11)
    - Fisher, Raymond, no date (Box 11)
    - Garvin, Charles, 1969 (Box 11)
    - Glasser, Paul H
      - 1962-1963 (Box 11)
      - 1965 (Box 11)
      - No date (Box 11)
    - Glasser, Paul H. and Costabile, Jane, 1963 (Box 11)
    - Glasser, Paul H. and Veurink, Allen, undated (Box 11)
    - Gold, Bertram H., 1946 (Box 11)
    - Lawrence, Harry and Connor, Alan, no date (Box 11)
    - Olerio, Catherine, 1967 (Box 11)
    - Pawlak, Edward J., 1963 (Box 11)
    - Peal, James A., no date (Box 11)
    - Psathas, George, 1960 (Box 11)
    - Radin, Norma, 1970 (Box 11)
    - Radin, Norma and Wittes, Glorianne, 1969-1970 (Box 11)
    - Rose, Sheldon D.
      - 1966 (Box 11)
      - Papers and audio tapes, 1967; 2 folders; 2 audiotapes 3 1/2 ips; reel-to-reel tapes (Box 11)
      - 1968 (Box 11)
    - Sarri, Rosemary C.
      - 1964 (Box 11)
      - 1966 (Box 11)
    - Sarri, Rosemary C. and Galinsky, Maeda J., 1964 (Box 11)
    - Sarri, Rosemary C. and Hasenfeld, Z., 1966 (Box 11)
    - Stern, Nell, 1962 (Box 11)
    - Theodorson, George A., undated (Box 11)
    - Vinter, Robert D.
      - 1959 (Box 11)
      - 1960 (Box 11)
      - 1961 (Box 11)
      - 1963 (Box 11)
      - 1966 (Box 11)
      - 1967 (Box 11)
      - Undated (Box 11)
    - Vinter, Robert D. and Conzemius, Rosemary, 1961 (Box 12)
    - Vinter, Robert D. and Sarri, Rosemary C
      - 1962 (Box 12)
      - 1964-1965 (Box 12)
    - Vinter, Sallie P., 1960 (Box 12)
    - Whittaker, James K., Undated (Box 12)
    - Wolfson, Charles
      - 1963 (Box 12)
      - 1965 (Box 12)
      - 1967 (Box 12)
      - 1970 (Box 12)
    - Unknown Author
      - Adult Probation Group, no date (Box 12)
      - Practice Skill Assessment Instrument, 1967 (Box 12)
  - Case Studies (Box 12)
  - ADC Mothers, 1963 (Box 12)
  - AFDC Mothers, 1966 (Box 12)
  - Behavioral Approach To Treatment Of Nocturnal And Diurnal Enuresis, no date (Box 12)
  - Boys Training School, no date (Box 12)
  - Camp Sequoia, no date (Box 12)
  - Camp Windy Knoll, 1951 (Box 12)
  - Children In A Child Guidance Center, no date (Box 12)
  - David At Camp, no date (Box 12)
  - Excerpts From Records Of Social Group Work Practice, 1951 (Box 12)
  - Forum Planning Committee, 1950 (Box 12)
  - Foster Home Licensors, 1964 (Box 12)
  - Fun Club, no date (Box 12)
  - Hilltop Girls Club, no date (Box 12)
  - Initiating A Token Economy, 1966 (Box 12)
  - Juvenile Court, 1967 (Box 12)
  - Jeff-Bright Community Club, no date (Box 12)
  - Male Patients In A State Mental Hospital, no date (Box 12)
  - The Meaning Of Play, no date (Box 12)
  - The Mother As Change Agent In The Treatment Of Her Daughter, undated (Box 12)
  - Myran Miller, 1950 (Box 12)
  - Name Changed, 1964 (Box 12)
  - The O Family, 1964 (Box 12)
  - The Pioneers, 1961-1962 (Box 12)
  - The Radio Club Record, 1950 (Box 12)
  - The Riester Family, undated (Box 12)
  - The Rolling '69ers, undated (Box 12)
  - Supervisory Practice In Group Work, 1950 (Box 12)
  - Senior CO-EDS, undated (Box 12)
  - Two ADC Mothers, 1963 (Box 12)
  - West Road Settlement House, Undated (Box 12)
  - Young Boys' Treatment Group, 1966 (Box 12)
- Curriculum, 1967-1994
  Curriculum, 1967-1994, contains course statements, which describe the requirements, and bibliographies for particular classes; they are arranged by the number of the course, information on discontinued courses and evaluation results from student surveys about the classes.
  - Course Statements
    - Course Statements, 1967-1973
      - 500: Social Welfare in the United States, 1967-1972 (Box 19)
      - 502: Analysis of Social Welfare Policy and Services, 1967-1973 (Box 19)
      - 513: Innovation and Change in Social Welfare Organizations, 1967 (Box 19)
      - 513: Social Work and Human Biology, circa 1991 (Box 19)
      - 514 and 519: Community Structure and Process/Societal Structure and Process, 1971-1973 (Box 19)
      - 516: Afro-American Culture and Life, circa 1970 (Box 19)
      - 517: Racism in American Society, circa 1970 (Box 19)
      - 523: Group Treatment III, circa 1970 (Box 19)
      - 530: Interpersonal Practice: Clinical Casework with Individuals and Couples, 1978 (Box 19)
      - 531: Social Treatment I, 1967-1982 (Box 19)
      - 532: Social Treatment II, 1967 (Box 19)
      - 533: Social Treatment III, circa 1970 (Box 19)
      - 534: Social Treatment IV, 1967 (Box 19)
      - 535: Behavioral Framework I, 1978 (Box 19)
      - 540: Effecting Organizational Change, circa 1970 (Box 19)
      - 551: Community Practice I, circa 1970 (Box 19)
      - 552: Community Practice II, circa 1970 (Box 19)
      - 561: Administration and Policy Records I, 1976 (Box 19)
      - 562: Social Welfare Administration and Policy Methods II, circa 1970 (Box 19)
      - 572: Social Welfare Policy Methods II, circa 1970 (Box 19)
      - 578: Policy and Planning Skill Instruction, 1980 (Box 19)
      - 579: Policy and Planning Skill Instruction Laboratory II, circa 1980 (Box 19)
      - 580: Research in Interpersonal Practice, 1981 (Box 19)
      - 592: Medical Information, circa 1970 (Box 19)
      - 593: Economics of Social Services, 1969-circa 1980 (Box 19)
      - 598: Social Treatment in the Inner City, 1968 (Box 19)
      - 601: Correctional Programs, 1968-1978 (Box 19)
      - 602: Family and Children's Programs, 1967-1980 (Box 19)
      - 603: Income Maintenance Programs, 1968-1980 (Box 19)
      - 604: Mental Health Programs, 1968-1972 (Box 19)
      - 605: Health and rehabilitation Programs, 1968-1975 (Box 19)
      - 606: Policy Making in Public Assistance, 1968-1975 (Box 19)
      - 607: Housing Programs, 1972-1975 (Box 19)
      - 608: Social Welfare Programs in Other Countries and Programs in Race and Ethnic Relations, 1968-1979 (Box 19)
      - 609: Social Services in the Schools, 1968-Spring/Summer 1976 (Box 19)
      - 609: Social Services in the Schools, Fall 1976-1981 (Box 19)
      - 610: Human Resources Programs, 1969-1981 (Box 19)
      - 612: Social Deviance, 1968-1983 (Box 19)
      - 613: Principles of Behavior Modification II, 1972-1982 (Box 19)
      - 614: Mental Disorders of Adults, 1972-1983 (Box 19)
      - 615: Comparative Personality Theories, 1972-1980 (Box 19)
      - 616: Mental Disorders of Children and Adolescents, 1972-1981 (Box 19)
      - 617: Political and Economic Behavior of the Black Community, 1972-1978 (Box 19)
      - 618: Social Movements and Social Reform, 1977-1980 (Box 19)
      - 619: Social Welfare Legislation and Social Change, 1967-1981 (Box 19)
      - 620: Social Stratification, 1967-1979 (Box 19)
      - 621: Social Treatment III, 1972-1982 (Box 19)
      - 622: Interpersonal Practice in Health Setting, 1972-1982 (Box 19)
      - 623: Advanced Interpersonal Practice with Children and Youth, 1978-1983 (Box 19)
      - 624: Interpersonal Practice: In Child Welfare, 1979-1981 (Box 19)
      - 625: Advanced Interpersonal Practice with Families, 1977-1994 (Box 19)
      - 631: Advanced Interpersonal Brief Clinical Casework, 1972-1982 (Box 19)
      - 632: Advanced Interpersonal Marital Clinical Casework, 1977-1983 (Box 19)
      - 633: Advanced Interpersonal Group Work Agency Context, 1978-1979 (Box 19)
      - 634: Comparative group Methods, 1977-1983 (Box 19)
      - 635: Behavioral Methods with Adults, 1978-1983 (Box 19)
      - 636: Extended Clinical Casework, 1977-1982 (Box 19)
      - 640: Community Mental Health Alternatives to Institutionalization, 1978-1980 (Box 19)
      - 646: Program Methods in group Work, 1973-1979 (Box 19)
      - 650: Community Development, 1979-1980 (Box 19)
      - 651: Social Action, 1968-1983 (Box 19)
      - 652: Committee Task Group and Board Management, 1972-1981 (Box 20)
      - 653: Social Planning, 1972-1982 (Box 20)
      - 654: Integrative Seminar, 1972-1981 (Box 20)
      - 655: Women and Community Organization, 1991 (Box 20)
      - 660: Personal Administration, 1976-1982 (Box 20)
      - 661: Informational Processing, 1967-1982 (Box 20)
      - 662: Supervision, 1972-1981 (Box 20)
      - 663: Staff Development and Training, 1972-1981 (Box 20)
      - 664: Models of Organizational Design, 1968-1972 (Box 20)
      - 665: Executive Leadership, 1972-1982 (Box 20)
      - 670: Administration and Policy Practicum, 1972-1982 (Box 20)
      - 671: Policy Analysis and Development, 1976-1982 (Box 20)
      - 672: Policy and Plan Implementation, 1972-1981 (Box 20)
      - 673: Budgetary and Fiscal Management Processes, 1977-1981 (Box 20)
      - 674: Program Design/Implementation, 1977-1981 (Box 20)
      - 675: Seminar in Social Program Evaluation, 1978-1981 (Box 20)
      - 676: Application of Research Methods, circa 1970 (Box 20)
      - 680: Administration Methods Seminar, 1977-1982 (Box 20)
      - 681: Application and Utilization of Research Methods, 1972-1981 (Box 20)
      - 682: Research in Complex Organizations, 1967-1981 (Box 20)
      - 683: Research in Interpersonal Influence, 1968-1981 (Box 20)
      - 684: Research in Community Practice, 1968-1981 (Box 20)
      - 685: Developmental Research, 1981 (Box 20)
      - 698: Programs and Services for the Aging, 1972-1983 (Box 20)
      - 701: Supervision in Practice Skill Instruction, 1977-1980 (Box 20)
      - 702: Rural Communities, 1977-1980 (Box 20)
      - 703: Introduction to Developmental Disabilities, 1973-1981 (Box 20)
      - 704: Human Sexuality, 1977-1978 (Box 20)
      - 704: Gender, Social Class and Disordered Behavior, 1979-1983 (Box 20)
      - 705: Psychological Testing and Social Work Practice, 1978-1983 (Box 20)
      - 706: Poverty and Economic Discrimination in U.S., 1976-1981 (Box 20)
      - 707: Cost-Benefit Analysis, 1977-1982 (Box 20)
      - 708: Special Studies in SWPS, 1976-1981 (Box 20)
      - 709: Special Studies in SWPS, 1976-1982 (Box 20)
      - 710: Special Topics, 1975-1982 (Box 20)
      - 712: Special Topics, 1976-1981 (Box 20)
      - 713: Industry, Work and Social Work, 1976-1982 (Box 20)
      - 714: Child Advocacy, 1976-1980 (Box 20)
      - 715: Introduction to Drug and Alcohol Programs, 1976-1979 (Box 20)
      - 716: Chicano Studies, 1974-1979 (Box 20)
      - 716: Counseling Older Adults and Their Families, 1978-1980 (Box 20)
      - 717: Right to Treatment and Death, Loss and Grief, 1974-1982 (Box 20)
      - 718: Advocacy Theory and Practice, 1976-1982 (Box 20)
      - 719: Special Topics, 1977-1979 (Box 20)
      - 722: Introduction to Interpersonal Methods, 1977-1981 (Box 20)
      - 723: Special Topics, 1977-1979 (Box 20)
      - 724: Special Topics, circa 1980 (Box 20)
      - 725: Interpersonal Practice, 1976-1980 (Box 20)
      - 726: Group Supervision, 1976-1979 (Box 20)
      - 727: Introduction to Interpersonal Practice Method, 1977 (Box 20)
      - 728: Group Leadership Techniques Alcohol Problems, 1975-1980 (Box 20)
      - 732: Social Work in Black Community, 1976-1981 (Box 21)
      - 733: Tools, Tactics and Techniques, 1980-1981 (Box 21)
      - 734: Collaboration with Community Caregivers, 1976-1980 (Box 21)
      - 735: Program Design, Implementation and Improvement, 1977 (Box 21)
      - 736: Budgetary and Fiscal Management Processes, 1977 (Box 21)
      - 737: Organizational Design, 1980 (Box 21)
      - 739: Policy: Evaluation and Planning of Alcohol Programs, 1977 (Box 21)
      - 740: HIV/AIDS: Programs, Policies, and Services, circa 1994 (Box 21)
      - 784: Human Sexuality: Issues for Social Work Practice, 1981 (Box 21)
      - 804: Empirical and Theoretical Foundations of Individual Change, 1980 (Box 21)
      - 805: Behavior Disorders and Variations, 1977 (Box 21)
      - 807: Principles and Techniques of Behavioral Interventions, 1978-1981 (Box 21)
      - 808: Principles and Processes of Interpersonal Change, 1977-1979 (Box 21)
      - 814: The Family as Target and Context for Social Change, 1977-1980 (Box 21)
      - 815: Socialization, 1979 (Box 21)
      - 817: Marital and Family Treatment, 1976-1978 (Box 21)
      - 818: Interpersonal Helping in Groups, 1978-1980 (Box 21)
      - 824: Human Service Organization, 1977-1981 (Box 21)
      - 827: Changing in Service Delivery, 1976-1980 (Box 21)
      - 828: Changing Social Service Networks, 1977 (Box 21)
      - 833: Special Topics, 1977-1978 (Box 21)